Siddhartha Chetri

7 years of experience in IT Network Telecom and Consulting Sector, Business Analysis, Infrastructure.Project Management & Coordination, Change & Incident Management. Good level of understanding of the ITIL framework. Strong hold in Project Management.

Bengaluru, Karnataka - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Siddhartha-Chetri/

f6959d21c6b91bba

A career with a progressive organization that will use my education and abilities in an executive

capacity, where that best matches my skills and experience to ensure a positive growth for the $\,$

organization and self.

Seeking challenging assignment in Customer Partner relation, Project/Change Management in Telecom and IT Sector.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Partner Sites Infosys, Concentrix, Merchants and Convergys

Collabera Technologies- Client- Cisco Systems, Inc -

July 2015 to Present

July 2015 - Till Date)

- Responsible for ensuring that all our Partner should get the Access Control List in right way and timely manner.
- Reporting regular stats on Case management, Infrastructure/Bandwidth utilization.
- Handling 4 Partner Sites Infosys, Concentrix, Merchants and Convergys.
- \bullet Working with different teams in the organization for streamlined output.
- SPOC for all the Partner Sites.
- Working as a Business Analyst/Project Coordinator in maintaining and delivering record for the project related work.
- Driving project/task for a new request from the Partner Site.
- To be an integral part of the project/task and help our Partners in achieving their goal.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Preparing process documents and Local Work Instructions (LWI) for the process.

Technology Associate / Incident Management

Magna Infotech- Client- Sapient Consulting -

July 2014 to July 2015

- \bullet Responsible for all the Incidents and Server Monitoring.
- ${f \cdot}$ Generating reports for project and service manager of all the Incidents and Problem tickets.
- · Analyzing of the price load report for our client in deployment stage.
- · Resolving of Incidents so that SLA won't be breached.
- Running of queries on putty on daily basis for message reprocessing for our client.

- Generating Deployment report for the overall item listed on our site for our Client.
- ullet Having exceptional interpersonal, verbal and written communication and motivational skills.
- · Hands on experience on Splunk for checking the logs of all the server.

https://www.indeed.com/r/Siddhartha-Chetri/f6959d21c6b91bba?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN

https://www.indeed.com/r/Siddhartha-Chetri/f6959d21c6b91bba?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN

- Ability to be results-oriented, a continuous learner, flexible, multitasking.
- Known tools: Splunk, Remedy, CA Introscope Workstation, TIBCO, Oracle Database.

Project / Service coordinator / Change Consultant

Cable & Wireless Worldwide/ Vodafone Global Shared Services Private Limited -

November 2011 to June 2014

November 2011- June 2014)

Project / Service coordinator / Change Consultant

• Manage & co-ordinate PSTN Service for M& S (Marks & Spencer), Centrica

projects involving Design, Planning phase for all UK Clients.

- · Expertise in making Project Plans & amp; Requirement Analysis.
- \bullet Expertise in report generation for different customers their services, circuits, affected servers.
- Develop, implement, and maintain the Project management plan, including risk management,

communication plan, and QA plan with the help of leads.

- · Define team member roles and expectations, and ensure timely feedback.
- ${\mbox{\tiny \bullet}}$ Having exceptional interpersonal, verbal and written communication and motivational skills.
- · Good knowledge of Business Analysis, Project Coordination process.
- Ability to be results-oriented, a continuous learner, flexible, multitasking.
- Training new colleagues who come into the team.
- Hands On experience on Incident, Change Management.
- ${\boldsymbol \cdot}$ Acknowledging, raising and worked on Incident tickets as well as CRQ request for our clients.

Tools Handled

• Remedy 7.6 to update track all the Changes that are going to be affected for our major

customers like Airtel, Tawasul, Fatsweb etc.

• Preparing Business case with the Project Manager.

Previous Organization/Duration/Roles:

iTunes Advisor/ Subject Matter Expert

Aditya Birla Minacs -

August 2010 to November 2011

Manage IT Infrastructure for the entire iTunes Process.

- Determine the project approach, staffing, responsibilities, and schedule.
- Define team member roles and expectations, and ensure timely feedback.
- Ensure that Colleagues receive timely updates on incidents.
- · Group Policy Management and Implementing Security Policies.
- Handling escalations.
- Ensuring that team meets CSAT, Quality, Productivity and SLA assigned.
- ullet Measure and monitor progress at milestones and ensure delivery as per schedule.
- Represent the project team at client meetings and provide project status details.

Responsibilities

- Worked as an iTunes Advisor troubleshooting customer problems related to Apple iTunes in timely manner.
- Generating reports on customer's request.
- Ensuring that team meets CSAT, Quality, Productivity and SLA assigned.
- Group Policy Management and Implementing Security Policies.
- In a short period become an SME.
- · Shown excellence in a very short period.
- Ensure that Colleagues receive timely updates on incidents
- Handling escalations.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Application in Computer Application

Administrative Management College Bangalore University - Bengaluru, Karnataka

2007 to 2010

SKILLS

REMEDY (3 years), CLARIFY (Less than 1 year), EXCEL (Less than 1 year), MS OFFICE (Less than 1 year), OUTLOOK (Less than 1 year)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skill Set:

- Systems: Windows [...] 10)
- Software: MS Office (Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint), Clarify, SRMS Remedy V6 (Advanced),

Remedy V7.4 (Proficient), Remedy 7.5, MORI, GCD, LOCM, GTOMS, Webex, Smartsheet.

Strengths:

- Adaptability
- Positive Attitude
- \bullet Quick learner with ability to learn new concepts, methods and technologies
- I believe in my ability to handle any situation
- Good customer relation management